

## **PROFILE**

22-year-old living in Breda.

Graduate year gameplay programmer studying International Game Architecture and Design at the Breda University of Applied Sciences.

Specializes in gameplay systems and virtual- and augmented-reality technologies.

Also experienced in leading a team of programmers as tech lead.

#### CONTACT

PORTFOLIO:

https://www.timhereijgers.com/

EMAIL:

timhereijgers@hotmail.com

# **LANGUAGES**

Dutch (native) English (fluent)

## **HOBBIES**

Hiking Photography Piano & Guitar

# TIM HEREIJGERS

Gameplay Programmer / VR&AR Specialist

# **EDUCATION**

## CSW van de Perre Highschool

August 2010 – July 2016 VWO level Education

# **Breda University of Applied Sciences**

August 2016-July 2020 (expected) Best Year 1 Game 2017 winner Best Year 2 Game 2018 winner

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## VR & AR Developer at KLM Royal Dutch Airlines

September 2019-Now

Coming up with and develop new innovative AR and VR software that can be used to excite users and introduce them to new realities.

## AR Developer for The Storyteller

November 2019-March 2020

Developing an AR application for the book "Pilot with the five stripes".

# Lead Programmer at Stellar Survivor

May 2019-July 2019

Overseeing development of 10 programmers, project management, maintaining quality of code architecture.

# Gameplay Programmer at Stellar Survivor

September 2018-April 2019

Creating game systems, managing stability, gameplay programming

## **Gameplay Programmer at Tiles Apart**

May 2018-August 2018

Creating game systems & gameplay programming

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Expert**

C#, C++, Unity, Unreal, OculusVR, SteamVR

#### **Proficient**

HTML, CSS, Java